Mary Edwards Walker Papers
Mary Edwards Walker Papers
- Writings
  - Pamphlets
    - Crowning Constitutional Arguement (Oswego, N.Y.), 1907 (Box 4)
    - Isonomy, 1898 (Box 4)
  - Reminiscences
    - Incidents connected with the Army, undated; 37 pages, typescript (Box 4)
    - On Mary Walker, undated; 6 pages, handwritten (Box 4)
  - By others
    - Commencement of Syracuse Medical College, 1855; photocopy of original, as published in the American Medical and Surgical Journal, Vol. VII, No. 4 (Box 4)
    - On women's dress, "By Prof. G. Edwin Churchill", undated; 1 page, handwritten copy (Box 4)